Astrology? What do the public for astrology?
. Recently ah, we've become Nndjem by smart our phones
! This kind of things can be done by phone? Show me! Show me
. H-Well
"Astrology is the moon"
! I'll tell you Bmasirk the status of the moon
Is not this Marica?
. No, her voice is similar represented by
..Hmmmm
Declaration of the Assembly Allantij-
- Well, here is your score
Ica, Could one say that the wall around your mind thin!?
. For this reason you are very frank, and Taatoven things as small
. For example, you're trying to take into account the feelings of others
! just awesome ! You have made me reassuring
. This is really a surprise, even to put it in the history of AD
! I went out and detailed answer as well as the blink of an eye
! Occultism commoners stunning
. Ah, I wrote the color of your luck here
! Huh? let me see
Okay ?
What is that ?
! Green is the color received
! If I have taken myself in this amount of green there is no doubt that I'll be lucky
... Okay
You will have to make your face Green, also
. Yes, as long as I got to the actual dimension continue all the way
Say what you have to do? Do Bkivta put something on them too?
Going on the road. You Ica, a beautiful idea
. Here we go, it is now ideal
... in order, and now you are carrying grain Alaedima Argosai Balorjae
"Certainly generate better with" pills, pills
when ?
. Dance when commoners brings good luck
- We do this before the beginning of the spring - before the spring?
We Nbosr grain on that day, you do commoners as well?
. Yes, and as long as did not arrive today evening spring, Doing this half remains effective
. Now, I've got the color of your luck and pills Alaedima hands
. You do according to
! But you can not use green soy beans in the evening spring
. The pills are the primary Idema soy beans
! I did not know it
! Well, Ica Argosai Orgosai for good luck
♪ pills! pills! ♪
♪ pills! pills! ♪♪ pills! pills! ♪ Here you Ica
"Now," Gates
"Gates"
! Again, from the top
Okay
♪ pills! pills! ♪
! Gates
who is she ?
"Declaration of results"
- Well, this is the result
. Rico, you are living in order to communicate with everyone who Tmlkinh
Episode 8 of the Ica-sama a lot of friends
, Due to the excellent ability in monitoring and analysis
. Vstagdin success in doing management
. You are fixed in your quest for Romancik
. just awesome ! I think it's incredibly accurate
Oh really ? Astrology Commoner accurate, true?
Well, Should we try this with you Haku?
... Haku, you Thafezin on a delicate balance between the conflicting natures
. Kalnchat, inactivity and attention and neglect
. Both suits you to be a researcher or artist
. This is true, well
. Occultism commoners stunning
! What an incredible civilization
Well, it's very accurate, is not it? That suits you to be a researcher
! What a tamper
What can the ability of astrology to say about me?
! It is impossible to fall in this absurd
In this case, you Tmaenai left?
you idiot
You want to try too, right?
! Only in the scope of the art of self-defense
. Well Well
... Well, I'm as they are talking about
... I bet he will say that I am an independent noble Hospitality
. Or like Maimutw Musashi years in the dusk, or something like that
. This is not what you have to say
. Karen, you're lonely too
. You are of the kind that does not stop worrying about everything around him
... You often stray, in your fear and perform tasks
. But smile wins easily and spontaneously, and you are inactive when it comes to romance
.Artvaa Anthwaitk is your charm
! E-there is something wrong
. No, I think it has Ahstk dramatically
! Let me see him, because you carry it got this ridiculous result
! I'll do this Biday
! Test your fit with the person who care about him
... for us for easy exercises in the vernacular activities
. I think it would be very useful for us to know Tuaqatna
- for - I was
So, why not use this vaunted grassroots astrology?
... With this it seems to be showing compatibility with the opposite sex
. For this we will use with Kemeto-sama as a binary for our examination
. Because this is the only way, we perception that we do not have another option
A-order, what would you do!?
. Hmm, it is the only option
! What gives all of this Agreement
. Well, Flandaoh day club activities
. I think it's no problem as long as it in this fun
. Well, Kemeto-sama please Start
E-Listen, you do not think that there was a strange atmosphere here?
Huh?
. Do not bother, nothing
. Well, we will begin to Arzogaoa-san
what is wrong with you ?
. . . Nothing, just
. P-Let's start with Ica-sama
Huh?
. In alphabetical order
- Well, we'll start with Bhetwafiqi Ica - e-hai, a-waiting
What is that ?
Okay ?
, Ah, give it points up
K-How many points?
... Let's see
Huh? How many ?
- Tell me, according to please and tell us faster
! Tell us what, come on
Haku, what Tdharban my knees?
.. Let's see ... I am consensual and Ica is
. 80 points, I was stunned at the first meeting
. And quickly fell in love
. Ica and Kemeto Ciecklna gorgeous duo no doubt in this
. Q-I was pleased because I thought it was good and enjoyed by
! But it was also a compromise with Kemeto
! So for this reason, it was a compromise with Kemeto
! Ah, fun nights
. كيميتو-ساما تنّبأ لي من فضلك تالياً
. الآن بعد ان فكرت بهذا فإن أرسوجاوا تأتي اولاً في الحروف الأبجدية
. آو ، ريكو هى التالية !؟ أتمنى ان تحصل على نقاط جيدة
. مع هذا أشك انها قد تحصل على نقاط أعلى من 80
. كما حصل فإن نقاطي 80
! كيميتو-ساما ، من فضلك أسرع واخبرنا النتيجة
. 90نقطة ، كيميتو و ريكو مناسبان جداً للزواج
. بالتأكيد ستهنئين بحياة زوجية سعيدة مع كيميتو
. 90نقطة ! و مناسبة جداً للزواج كذلك
! هذا خطأ ! هناك خطأ في الإدخال او شيء من هذا القبيل
. اوه ، هيا آيكا-ساما
. علينا ان نكون سعيدتين لأن كلانا حصل على نتيجة جيدة
. من جهتي ، انا سعيدة جداً
. آيكا-ساما ، لقد حصلتِ على ... 80نقطة حسب ما أذكر
هاكو  ؟ ماذا عنك؟ أتريدين المحاولة ؟
. أتسائل كم سيكون توافقي مع هاكو
. هناك بعض المصطلحات الفرعية الغير مفهومة تماماً في اللعبة هنا
... 50نقطة ، يبدو أن تفاعلك مع هاكو
. ليس جيد ولا سيء
.. لأن هاكو من النوع الذى يُفهم على نحو خاطئ كثيراً
. فسيكلفكم فهم بعضكم البعض مجهود أكبر
. إنها مرتبكة قليلاً بسبب النتيجة السيئة التى خرجت
حـ-حسناً ،  إنه تنجيم ، أتريدون بعض الشاي ؟
هاكو ؟
. حسناً
هـ-هاكو-ساما هل أحضر بعض الحلوى الجديدة ؟
. هذه فكرة جيدة ، سأذهب لأحضرهم
. لا أعتقد ان هذا يزعجها لهذا الحد
اذن ، ماذا عنكِ كارين ؟
. لا يمكنني ان اكون الوحيدة التى لم تحاول
. هل انتِ متأكدة ؟ لا سبب لإجبار نفسك على فعل هذا
اوه ، آسف آسف ، فلنفعلها
! انا لا اريد تحديداً فعل هذا ، أتفهم؟
. أجل ، أجل
. 0نقطة ، لو كنتِ مع كيميتو فإنه سيموت
يموت ؟
!... لـ-لما ، انتِ
لما تحاولين قطعي ؟
هاي ، التنجيم كان دقيق جداً
. هذا لا يشكل أيّ فارق
. لا يُأخذ التنجيم كإثبات اننا غير متوافقين
. الجميع علم هذا منذ البداية
أيمكنك التوقف عن طعن السجّاد بالكاتانا خاصتك ؟
. اوه ، آسف ، لقد اخطأتُ في مدخلاتك
ماذا ؟
... تاريخ ميلادك لم يُدخل ، فلنرى
. 100نقطة ،انتم شركاء حتميين
. كارين و كيميتو مثاليين معاً ، لا طريقة أخرى للتعبير عن هذا
. انتِ الشريك النهائي ، التى يمكنها الإرتباط معه على المستوى الروحي العميق
.كارين ، يجب عليِك بداية هجومك بقوة واستعجال بدءاً من الغد
. العبي بمهاراتك الخاصة و انقضِ عليه بأشد ما يمكنك
100نقطة !؟
! هاي ، لا تأخذِ الأمر على محمل الجد
إنه مجرد تنجيم
--أجل
-- بطبيعة الحال ، إنه ليس بهذه الدقة
-- لا يمكنك الإيمان بهذا الشيء
-- هذا صحيح
كنتما متحمستان قبل دقيقة عن مدى دقته ، اليس كذلك ؟
! اعطه لي
" سنيزلق بعيداً عنك ببطئ "
خطأ ! هذا ليس التنجيم الحقيقي الذى اريده
" كلاكما لديه أقوى العلاقات الكريمة منذ الأزل "
. اسم سيد التنجيم اونميوجي قد وضع
لدى آيكا-سان الكثير من الأصدقاء " هذا خطأ"
. آه ، لم نجرب هذا التنجيم بعد
-- حسناً،  هذه
-- التالي ، سنقوم بهذه
! فلنجرب هذه وحسب
" اخيراً وجدته انا وكيميتو " مرتبطين بشكل مثالي بلا زيادة لقولها
طالما انتِ و كيميتو " في رأس ريكو تماماً " فهو دقيق للغاية
... What are you talking about, this astrology says
"Kemeto and Rico are partners, selected Saosson happy house"
"Says your fit" Ica snail produces pressure on Kemeto
! I'm not spiral
How you could say this
. I'm sure that any compatibility with me will never matter
! that is enough
! Both of you, Aofaqa Khalavkma
! Disgraceful to us that we fight on one of us Tnjimh true
! True astrology comes from the moon, the mine in uniform sea
- No, not as well as you've already wrong
- This is the only pictured Alhanaoal with proper astrology
... will be out to individual inspiration for the birth of true astrology
what is wrong with you ?
. I'm hungry
! Uh, well, I'm going to something
. I want potato cakes
Oh, I loved? is not it ?
.. I wonder if I have any potato
! Hotkik will be good as well
Well, Are we together?
are you awake ?
... a-order
. I wished I never wake up
Have you signed in the ring?
--- Listen, there's something you want to question him
As always you stand there Watching waking?
Kojo-san?
Is there any rule stipulates that my answer to your questions?
. No, there is not
.Lsu luck, we're the maid who serve you
. Unfortunately, it wakes you up from my duties
. In fact, the best that Atjahlha, but as head of servants
. It hurts me that I can do this because I managed to seal my feet frustrated
Do you deliberately Stmtina four times?
- I'm annoying - this fifth
. Therefore, the settlement that hit them until you wake up is watching
... This is not within your business, right?
. Mchahtk within my work
. This reminds me of the announcement Old, you will not get any white liquid filtered from me
Is this sexual harassment?
! No ! Apply this scissors aside
. You should not wake me anymore
. In a telephone alarm
. As you wish
. So now destroy your phone
when ?
. Excessive mechanics is the curse factor
And you do not work in the first place, is not it?
. Very good, that you are serious as well as Egypt Vsosubh
- No, you should not force yourself - every morning, I will put an ice rink and Adoor
. The three-axis Aoukzk serious
انا غير متأكد ايٌّ مكان يحتوي على كلمة " جادة " بالظبط
اذن ، علينا الإستمرار بنفس الطريقة التى بدأنها حتى الآن ؟
هاه  أجل
. سأخرج الآن لهذا من فضلك ارتدى ملابسك بسرعة
ما خطبها ؟
" آه اوه ، كتفاي "
" جعلتني غاضباً الآن "
هذه مرتي الاولى التى أراهم فيها لكن هذه
لكن هذه العبارات في الفيديو مضحكة جداً
ماذا هناك ؟
.كارين ، يجب عليِك بداية هجومك بقوة واستعجال بدءاً من الغد
. العبي بمهاراتك الخاصة و انقضِ عليه بأشد ما يمكنك
! فن السيف ، نمط كارين
القرار
ماذا ؟
ماهذا ؟ أيام برية باكوماتسو ؟
كاجورزاكا
أجل ؟
! مهاراتي الخاصة مع سيفي
هاه ؟
كيف هى ؟ مذهلة  ،صحيح ؟
... ا-اتو
! سألتك ان كانت مذهلة
! مذهلة ! مذهلة
انهم جيدة
لما بدأت الآن باللعب بمهاراتها الخاصة ؟
اوه ، ما هذا ؟
ماذا هناك ، كاجورزاكا ؟
كُم سترتك قد قطعت بوضوح اليس كذلك ؟
انت من قطعها
! لا فائدة ؟ سأصلحها لك
هاه ؟
.لا أملك اي معدات خياطة في متناول يدي ، لهذا سنذهب لغرفتي
. هذا وقتٌ جيد لك
.. هـ-هاي
. هذه غرفتي
مذهل
ما الذى يمكنني قوله ، انها بسيطة
. بالتأكيد ، هؤلاء الذين يسيرون على خُطى السيافون لا حاجة لهم بزينة لا فائدة منها
البساطة
و
الثبات
. اجلس هناك ، سأعد الشاي
. حـ-حسناً
. اشرب
. حسناً ، شكراً لك
" حار ، وخزة أذن "
ما خطبك ، كاجوزراكا ؟
. لـ-لاشيء
. حسناً ، سأجلب عدة الخياطة
. فلنرى ، أعلم انها هنا بمكان ما
هل هذا متعمد ؟ هل تقوم بهذا عمداً ؟
م-ماذا هناك ، كاجوزراكا ؟
هاه ؟
. أشعر ببصرك على ظهري
. لـ-لا ، انت تتخيلين الاشياء
.. ا-اوه
مجموعة الخياطة
. يا الهى ، يالك من رجل غريب الاطوار
! انت هى غريبة الاطوار هنا
. أوه ، اجل نسيت
. كاجورزاكا ، ادر ظهرك لي
لما ؟
! افعل هذا وحسب
ماذا ؟ لا تقل لي انها تقلع ملابسها
. ح-حسنا
ح-حسنا ؟
... أ-أجل
. البرزو الناتج عن تضخم هذه الأفخاد الجذابة
. ان تكون مقيدة بشدة بهذه الملابس الحارة بشكل جيد جداً
! اريد فرك خدي عليهم الآن وحسب
! سأدفع بكل سرور 1000 ين
. الخط الذى يتبعها من الأعلى لركبتيها مثالي كذلك
. The method of gloss, which reflected her skin tight
- make it seem very vigilant - I think it's good, I know, I said this earlier
. For-do not get me wrong
. It is light and open, I enjoy Bartdaihm
. Still it looks great on you, you look amazing out
. Well, maybe I will continue wearing from now on and other times
! But it will not be for you in any way
. True, I know
! You do not know
... This is a beautiful, what I can say, it's surprising
For what to happen?
. Oh, I was thinking and by how much you are a good bride
What-What are you talking about?
... e-Would you say
! No ! I'm not ready for this
! Stmezkinh !! Stmezkinh!
. Well, we finished
! Stunning, you can to look at a very close look, otherwise you will never learn that he has stitched
. What do you think ? This is the second after my skills fencing
. Yes, this is really amazing, my mom can not do this
So you call me carelessly to meet your parents, right?
Huh?
Internal cut your shirt, as well?
. Oh, you're right
. Oh well, as well as to sew, give me
Huh? No, nothing wrong
! aflha vhsb
. If I'd be half of his castle Nude
! This is what I am going to him
Huh?
Are you fine ?
. Yup
. Sorry
You have the hands of the poor, huh?
Huh?
. It's really different for girls
. But not as if by nothing special
How it was strong enough to overcome this?
Am I a strong grip for this limit?
. All his campaign with them is my sword
. Sometimes I am concerned about what is right to do
.. especially in the previous time I mean, as a girl, this
Prominent, is not it?
... Kajorzaka
This is a testament to how hard the work that you've done, right?
. And the harshness of your hand muscles in your arm
It has been built from one through which I walked by, right?
This kind of things up for others and have you received as you know
.. I think what Tortah as a result of something you've done
. I want to say it's a beautiful
K-Kajorzaka, Are you serious?
... Are you saying that I ..
! We have come
. nobody is here
Huh?
. But I heard them say they saw an amazing room Kemeto Karen
Well, where are they?
I thought I understood the ethics of all this world expanding
I thought so it's enough to follow what leads me to him daily
. But here I am here, I can not put a name to this
Feelings that can not be predicted, and the usefulness of the guide
The dividing line between the cheek mixing red, dark blue
And before I know about it, it made it hard to say inside or outside my heart
Do not disappear in the twilight, near to see what it all I
I'm sure that everything will be an opportunity to love
Bring your tears and your dreams, which are forced to hide your smile Well?
I will come to you days that you will Mhassoda everyone
Translation of Vergil vergil-sub.blogspot.com
Translation of Vergil Vergil-sub.blogspot.com waited for the coming of our translation episodes
. Since this idea, no need to hide them
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go for this
I love thee, O
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
I am deeply fascinated by the commoners
I Odrsk every day
You did not pick up telepathically so far?
what are you ? cool ?
Oh, you understand, you hide Khgelk, huh?
Such as the kind of love Confect
Which melt in my mouth
Pulse in my heart
Sweet and puzzling
I am ready to go
Here's my love of
I will give you all the feelings of my heart
. E-Hai, do not move
! I do not know how you could say this and you are in this position
! S-I said do not move
! Wah .. There is no
! Kemeto Kemeto-sama
Kemeto, what do you do?
What is that ?
. E-This is a new type of astrology
. Oh, so then
Otakbrha Astrological, huh?
So, you have no choice but to do this, huh?
Huh?
! Come on ! Astrological told her, come on
"Djalteni angry now."
come on hurry up
What do you mean that I made you angry now?
"Djalteni angry now."
Next Episode
Love Love, Mio-Mio
! You pervert
I am, I will be your servant Kemeto-sama
! Aflleha, really
! stop this
Kemeto, also gather them
! Mio-Mio, Kerr-Bio
Kajorzaka-sama here